

# RIVONNY WULANDARI

WEB & APP DEVELOPER

+62895634864912 | rivonnywulandari19@gmail.com linkedin.com/in/rivonnywulandari | rivonnywulandari.github.io/portofolio Padang, West Sumatra, Indonesia

#### **Summary**

A current senior majoring in Information Systems at Universitas Andalas. I completed an internship at Diskominfotik Sumbar, where I gained practical experience in database design and web development. In addition, I also did a freelance project related to GIS website. My fields of interest include Web Application, Mobile Application, and UI/UX Design.

## **Work Experience**

#### Freelance Web Developer | Mar 2023 - Nov 2023

Freelance - Padang, Indonesia

- Built a GIS campus map web for Universitas Andalas using PHP, Codelgniter4, OpenRouteService API and MySQL.
- Designed and analyzed system, user, and data requirements through observation of campus buildings, interviews with campus leaders, and study research.
- Built using Model-View-Controller architecture to implement create, read, update, delete (CRUD) with Codelgniter and OpenStreetMap API to perform spatial functions and present spatial data on map.

#### Web Developer Intern | Jan 2022 - Mar 2022

Department of Communication, Information Technology, and Statistics of West Sumatra (Diskominfotik Sumbar) - Padang, Indonesia

- · Analyze and discussed with programmers to create website interface of DPRD Sumatera Barat.
- · Work with programmer to manage the database design of the DPRD Sumatera Barat.
- · Complete program code of DPRD Sumatera Barat Website with PHP and Codelgniter Framework.

#### Education

#### Universitas Andalas | Jul 2019 - Nov 2024 (Expected)

Bachelor Degree in Information Systems

- 2nd place in the national-level GerakanLAA Essay Competition organized by FTI Universitas Andalas in 2020.
- 3rd Place in the national-level Epsilon Essay Competition organized by HIMA Statistika, Padang State University in 2022.
- Representing the Faculty of Information Technology, Universitas Andalas as an Outstanding Student (MAPRES) in the MAPRES Election at the Universitas Andalas level in 2022.
- Mentor for Diskas Application in the Social Project Competition INNOVILLAGE 2022 Diskas Activities on November 2022.

## **Organizational Experience**

# Laboratory of Geographic Information System (LABGIS) | 2020 - 2023

Assistan Coordinator

- Member of the Household Division and carrying out the LPJ Labgis filing program in the 2020/2021 year management.
- Head of the Research and Development Division and carried out the program for updating the organization's website as well as being a speaker on internal upgrading regarding QGIS in 2022 in the 2021/2022 year management.
- Become an Assistant Coordinator in the 2022/2023 year management.

# Information System Department Students Association of Universitas Andalas (HMSI) | 2021 - 2022 Member of the Public Relations Division

- Responsible for the implementation of the HMSI School Visit work program at SMAN 11 Padang in March 2022.
- Become a member of the 2022 HMSI Regeneration Committee.

#### **Skills**

- Hard Skills: PHP, JavaScript, Codelgniter, Laravel, Kotlin, Java, SQL, Python, C++, GIS, MySQL, PostgreSQL, Firebase.
- Interpersonal: Responsible, fast learner, leadership, flexible work hours, able to work in teams and individuals.
- Interest: Web and app application, UI/UX design, front-end development, back-end development, data analysis, GIS.
- Languages: Indonesian Native, English Intermediate (TOEFL ITP Prediction Score: 520).